rosettastoneclassroom.com 2012-05-10

# Overview

Rosetta Stone Ltd (“Rosetta Stone”) is the developer of the Rosetta Stone® language learning
programs. We take the privacy of our customers seriously. We are committed to safeguarding
your privacy while providing a personalized and valuable service
Overview
This Privacy Policy statement explains the data processing practices of Rosetta Stone. If you
have any requests concerning your personal information or any questions about these practices
please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com. We
encourage you to periodically review this statement as it may change at any time at our sole
discretion.
Our site contains links to third party sites, which are not subject to this privacy policy. Rosetta
Stone does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices or content on these sites.
We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any such sites that you visit.
Information provided by you may be requested from one of our websites under the Rosetta Stone
or Rosetta World brand names, or from one of our reputable co-marketing partner sites that
represent our brands on their own websites under their company and/or brand name. In the event
that you provide us with personal information for the purposes of free registration and you later
make a purchase, whether directly from us or facilitated by one of our e-commerce partners, your
privacy rights will be protected according to our stated policies and the stated privacy policies of
these partners, which will be posted and available for your review at the time of purchase.
Information Collected
Personal information is collected by Rosetta Stone. We collect personally identifiable
information about you (your “Data”) through:
       The use of inquiry and registration forms.
       The purchase process when you buy any of our products or services
       The provision of your details to us either online or offline
The elements of your Data that we collect may include:
       Name
       Job title
       Company name
       Home, shipping and billing addresses, phone and fax number
       Mobile telephone number
       E-mail address
       IP address and browser information
       Payment details such as credit card information
       Market research data such as customer usage patterns
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
REV102510

We use your Data for purposes, which may include:
        Providing our customers with a personalized service.
        Processing orders, registrations and inquiries.
        Conducting market research surveys.
        Running competitions.
        Measuring interest in and improving our website, products, and services.
        Providing you with information about products and services we offer. You may stop the
         delivery of marketing emails by following the instructions accompanying a particular
         communication or by contacting us at privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com.
        Resolving disputes, collecting fees, and troubleshooting problems.
We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete that order. We do not
share this information with outside parties except 1. To the extent necessary to complete that
order or to provide services where the outside party is acting on our behalf and has no
independent right to use the information we provide (e.g., third-party shipping, business analytics,
or customer support ), or 2. To successors in title to our business, or 3. In accordance with legal
and regulatory requirements, or 4. As necessary, in Rosetta Stone‟s sole discretion, to protect the
perceived rights, safety and property of Rosetta Stone, users of our websites, and the public.
Other than as set out above, you will be notified when Personal Information about you will be
shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such
information.
We also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified):
        To build up marketing profiles
        To aid strategic development
        To audit usage of the site
Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Devices
We use cookies to help personalize your use of our sites. A cookie is a small piece of
information which is sent to your computer‟s hard drive by the web server so that the website
can remember who you are. This information may include information relating to your use of our
sites, information about your computer such as the computer‟s IP address and browser type,
demographic data and, if you arrived at our site via a link from a third party site, the URL of the
linking page. If you are a registered user this may include your name and email address for
verification purposes.
We use information from cookies for purposes, which may include:
        Identifying returning users and registrants
        Enabling you to move more easily around our site
        Tracking your use of our site to better develop our sites in accordance with your
         requirements

       Building up a demographic profile.
       If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and
        marketing strategy, you may choose to set your Web browser to not accept cookies.
        Further information on how to prevent cookies from being stored on your computer can
        be found on http://www.allaboutcookies.org under the „manage cookies‟ section.
        Alternatively go to the help menu within your Internet browser.
From time to time we may permit 3rd party companies to set cookies on Rosetta Stone sites for
purposes which may include market research, revenue tracking or to improve functionality of the
site.
Security Policy
Rosetta Stone has appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users‟ Data is protected
against unauthorized access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental
loss. Although we make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information from loss,
misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved
in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that thieves could find a
way to thwart our security systems.
Transfer of Data
The Internet is a global environment. Using the Internet to collect and process personal Data
necessarily involves the transmission of Data on an international basis. When we collect
personal information from you on our website, we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor
Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and
retention of personal data from the European Union.
Access to Data and Contact Info
You may request a copy or send a correction of the personal information we hold about you by
contacting the Privacy Officer at privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com or writing to:
Privacy Officer
Rosetta Stone Ltd.
135 West Market Street
Harrisonburg VA 22801
USA
We may charge the allowable fee under applicable law for provision of this information.
Children Under 13

This site is not intended for use by persons under thirteen (13) years of age. We do not
intentionally collect any information on children under 13 years of age. We will undertake to
delete any details of such users where a parent or guardian has notified us that any such details
have been obtained.
Changes to this Policy
This policy is effective October 25, 2010. From time to time we may make changes to this
privacy policy statement to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with
changes in legislation, best practice or website enhancements. We will notify you about material
changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by
placing a prominent notice on our website.
